- Previously on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Come here.
[laughs]
- It's hard to treat Luke
the same as the other
relationships here.
- I'm being completely honest
with you.
When I look you
in the eyes... [laughs]
I see my future wife.
- There is a connection
between us
that is unlike anything
that I've experienced.
- This is what I want...
- Yeah.
- For the rest of my life.
- I feel like we're starting
to enter into a new chapter
of our relationship.
- So let's talk about sex.
- Okay.
- You know,
sex is an--an incredible thing.
Well, only...
[tense music]
You know, when it's in the--
within the guidelines
of marriage.
If you told me
you were having sex
or you had sex with one
or multiple of these guys...
I would be wanting to go home.
- Mm-hmm.
- 100%.
- I'm, like, kind of mad...
[chuckles]
because...
to have you say this about me
and judge me
or make me feel
like you would not think of me
as a woman of faith.
You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do.
It's just sex for you,
and that you're like,
"If you've had sex,
then I'm going home."
It's like,
"Well, I want somebody
"who can get along with people,
who doesn't have pride issues."
Like, there's so many things
that I don't want out of
a husband that you've shown.
And I feel like I've finally
gotten clarity on you.
And I do not want you
to be my husband.
[intense music]
- I feel like
you owe me at least...
- I don't owe you anything
at this point.
Do you not understand that?
♪ ♪
Please, get up.
[chuckles darkly] Oh, my God.
My husband would never say
what you've said to me.
I answer to the Lord.
I don't answer to Luke.
So, like, I have had sex.
- Say what?
- And Jesus still loves me.
- [groans]
- I feel a weight lifted off
my shoulders.
♪ ♪
[shimmering tones]
- Good evening,
Bachelor Nation.
I'm Chris Harrison,
and welcome
to what will be
a very different version
of "The Men Tell All."
This is sure to be
a shocking and emotional night.
Hannah's journey to find love
has been anything but easy,
and it's not about to get
any easier here tonight.
Usually, we start the tell-all
with all the guys out here
recapping the season,
but not tonight.
Tonight, we're picking up
where we left off:
in Greece,
where what happened
was so shocking,
we just couldn't wait
to show you.
So let's take a look.
[musical sting]
[wind rustling]
[soft music]
- This is my last
Rose Ceremony
and the hardest.
I have three amazing guys.
I have Peter,
Tyler,
and Jed.
All of my dates and overnights
went amazing.
I have been loved
so fearlessly
and so wholeheartedly.
- Peter.
Welcome.
- Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- Good to see you, man.
- Yeah, you too.
- How're you doing?
- I have...
truly never felt for someone
as much as I feel for Hannah.
- Right.
- And...
I'm crazy in love with her.
I just--I look forward
to an amazing future
with her, hopefully.
- The smile on your face
says it all.
- [laughs] Thank you.
Yeah.
- All right, you're gonna
head down to the right.
- All right. Hey.
- Good luck today.
- Thanks a lot.
Appreciate it.
- Bye, Peter.
- See you.
[romantic piano music]
- I do love all of them
in completely different ways,
so it's really hard--
like, moving forward
and hurting them.
♪ ♪
Because it's like breaking up
with someone
that I know
is someone who loves me
and that I care for
and have fallen
in love with too.
- Tyler, how're you doing?
- Doing well. How are you?
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome.
How you feeling?
- I feel amazing.
I feel really confident.
I feel really good, so...
We had a really special night.
We really connected a lot
and built so much more
in our relationship,
and, yeah, I'm just so excited
where things
are heading with us.
I love this girl.
She's--she's a special girl.
- All right.
Good luck.
- Thank you.
- I feel like I know
what I'm gonna do
going into the Rose Ceremony,
but I just need to assess
how I feel when I see them all
and make sure
that I'm comfortable
with the decisions
that I think I'm going to make
going in.
♪ ♪
- Jed.
How you feeling?
[cheers and applause]
- I feel good.
- Yeah?
- I do.
Um, there were just
a lot of questions I had.
[inhales]
I feel better.
- Yeah.
- I got a lot of clarity.
- I'll see you in there
in a little bit.
- Thanks Chris. See you.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- All in all, I wanted clarity
this week,
and I've heard everything
the men have said
about Luke P.
I finally was hit...
right in the face with what
everybody else was seeing.
I'm like, "I now can relate,"
and I sent Luke home.
And the other guys
have no idea.
- [whispering] Now we get
to wait for the great Luke.
[suspenseful music]
- I have no regrets.
I feel
like, "[bleep] that guy."
And not an ounce of me
misses him,
wants him in my life,
or will
question my decisions.
I'm so glad Luke
is finally gone
and I never
have to see him again.
[crowd groaning]
- Hannah thought...
[light laughter]
after sending me
in the van, that...
there's no way
I'd wanna be with her anymore
after the last thing
she told me.
And...
she's sadly mistaken.
She doesn't realize
that I still love her
and that I'm--
I'm not through.
This isn't over for me yet.
I couldn't--
I couldn't leave and go home
without talking to her again
and sharing my heart with her
and getting a few things
off my chest.
[disconcerting music]
♪ ♪
And I know she's never told me
that she loves me,
but I know she loves me.
And I know,
without a shadow of a doubt,
she still has feelings for me.
And I believe
she's making a big mistake.
And I'm going to tell her that.
She doesn't--
she doesn't know it yet...
but I'm on my way,
and I'm coming.
♪ ♪
[audience gasps]
I wanna prove to her
how serious I am about this.
♪ ♪
- Hey there.
- Hello.
- [laughs] How're you doing?
- I'm good.
- Good to see you.
♪ ♪
[music darkens]
- Here comes our favorite.
- Yup.
♪ ♪
[audience gasping, laughter]
[befuddled laughter]
♪ ♪
- There's now three men.
Two roses to hand out today.
- Mm-hmm.
- And so,
one of these guys
is gonna be going home.
- I'm dreading it.
- Yeah.
- Like, I'm excited
about my future
and how this week went,
but...
I know that
there is a man
that is not expecting
what is about to happen.
- Yeah.
- Do you know
what you're gonna do
for sure?
- Yes,
but, like,
it literally changed in a day.
- Yeah? Okay.
Good luck.
Head on in.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music building]
- [quietly] Hey.
- Why are you here?
- I--I need to talk
to you real qui--
- No.
- Listen.
I can't go home
until I talk to you
and get a few things
off my heart.
- No.
[cheers and applause]
[clears throat]
- She said no, bro. Just...
- Yeah.
- Walk back in line, man.
- No. Just go.
I've already--
go.
- Hannah.
I'm gonna stand here all day
until you--
- No the [bleep] you're not.
Just get away from me.
- Take a hint.
[cheers and applause]
I'm about to go psycho,
so...
please, leave.
- I need clarity right now.
- I have clarity.
It's--this is not about you.
- I understand that,
but I'm not leaving
until I at least have closure.
- Well...
[stammers, laughs]
[inhales deeply] Yeah,
you will leave,
because I've already
sent you home.
That's not--
that's not how this works.
[laughter and applause]
Since we have ended,
I have gone back
and thought of things
over and over in my head...
now that I've had
this clarity
about us,
and how much
of all this [bleep]
that I've put
everybody through--
all these people through--
that I've been a freaking
emotional roller coaster
is because of
giving you chances
to give me clarity.
And so,
I'm not doing this anymore.
And I'm not going to let you
rewrite what you said
the other night.
- I'm not here to rewrite
or change anything.
How relationships work
is through communication.
- Well, you--
- And l--listen, I'm...
[laughter]
This is my heart
we're talking about here.
This is a relationship.
- It's--this is not
about your heart!
- You--you never--
- [bleep]! Leave!
I'm just so--
I'm so tired
of you c--this is--
you're so narcissistic,
and it's always about
"my this, my that, my that."
It's not.
This is not about your heart.
I'm sorry that
your heart's broken,
but you've already
broken my heart, like,
15 times through all this
by me, like,
trying to make this work,
so I'm sorry
if I'm breaking your heart--
- My heart isn't broken yet
'cause I'm still standing here,
and this isn't--
and this isn't over for me yet.
- Oh, my God.
Well...
all right.
[laughter and applause]
- Luke. Luke, take a hint.
- You need to--
- Luke, just leave, dude.
- Did you or did you not
talk to Colton
after you got sent home...
- [laughs]
- To find closure?
- Bro.
- Luke, dude.
- Hannah--
- Dude, just let her--
- Can you guys--
- No--
- Can you guys give me
a minute?
- Dude, we've given you
plenty of minutes, dude.
- Listen.
Lay your hands off me.
- Or what?
[climactic music]
- Yeah. What are you gonna do?
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
- Why are you still here?
- She said no.
How many more noes do you need?
- Did you already
send him home, Hannah?
- Yeah.
- All right, then let's go.
- I'm telling your right now.
I'm not going anywhere...
until I get a chance
to share with you
how I feel right now.
- Get the [bleep] out.
- Dude, you sound pathetic
right now.
- Move.
Go.
- Do you want
to see yourself go?
- Wh--why are you doing this?
This is no--this is not the
same thing as me and Colton.
I did not treat him the same--
- I am not saying
this is the same.
- But you're like,
"I need this and that.
- I'm saying,
how can you not understand
where I'm coming from?
I'm just trying
to explain a few things to you.
- I don't understand,
like, why you need closure
because I have given you
so many opportunities,
and you tell--
- This will be--
this will be really easy
if you just give me...
about 60 seconds to talk.
- You've had more chances
than anyone here, dude.
- And actually listen to me.
- Just go.
- Why can't you just
get this message, dude, like...
- Take a hint.
- You know that
you were leading
with your emotions
the other night.
I know those last few minutes,
that was not your character.
- Why are you telling her
who she is, bro?
- And you totally
didn't understand
what I was trying to tell you
the other night.
- I'll--I'll--
I'll let everybody know
what you said the other night.
'Cause you literally asked me,
"Did you have sex--
if you've had sex
with anybody here," and--
[both chuckle]
- You're such a joke, bro.
- "Because if you've had sex
with somebody here,
"gone into a Fantasy Suite
"then I would remove myself
from here and go home,
but I know
you wouldn't do that."
- I didn't say that
word for word.
- You absolutely did.
- I don't want
to be misunderstood
and that be
the reason why I leave.
'Cause I--I know deep down...
after everything you told me...
- This guy's so pathetic.
- Throughout
this whole process,
I still know for a fact that
you still have feelings for me.
- I did have feelings for you
way longer than I wanted to,
and listened to everybody
say things and...
And explored my heart
and tried to figure it out,
but...
I've been praying for clarity
and praying for it,
and the moment...
[snaps]
That you started talking,
and the--
and what you were saying,
you were judging.
The way that you talk is not
the way that I talk about...
things.
- I 100% was misunderstood,
and I know for a fact...
That you didn't understand
what I was trying to tell you,
and never have I ever
condemned or judged you.
Ever.
And never will I ever,
so please don't put those words
in my mouth.
- There's nothing
to really talk about.
The Lord has allowed
that soul-tie,
weird spiritual thing
that I had with you
to completely be gone.
I haven't cried.
I have been like,
"What the crap happened
the other night?"
There has not been
one part of me that has had
any regret from what I've done,
so, no, you don't know...
how I feel.
- So, Hannah...
- Yeah?
- What do you want?
This is all up to you.
- I have been very clear
about every decision
I've made this--thus far,
and I was clear
the other night.
- Yeah.
- So I...
don't want him to be here.
- Okay.
- Can you seriously
look me in the eyes and tell me
that you have complete clarity,
and that you have
no feelings for me any longer?
- I can.
- Okay.
That's all I needed to hear.
- All right.
- I'll excuse myself.
- What the [bleep]?
- This way?
- Geez.
- Dude...
[tense music]
- Dude, he's so...
- What a--
- I mean, it's like...
- What a freakin'...
♪ ♪
- She sent him home, but,
like...he just won't leave.
♪ ♪
- I [bleep] hate that guy.
- You all right?
- Yeah. [laughs]
- Oh, what a joke.
- Well, the clarity
you were looking for...
- [chuckles]
- Now you have even more of it.
- Yeah.
- He is fully convinced--or was
that you are his wife,
that you are the one,
and that...nobody knows
the depths
of your relationship.
♪ ♪
He has a ring in his pocket
right now.
He was ready to propose to you.
♪ ♪
I know.
I'm not joking.
♪ ♪
- The Luke P. show's over now,
boys.
Thank God.
[laughter]
- Oh, my God.
[giggles]
I've been waiting for this,
and I'm so--I'm just glad
that she could finally see it.
I've never been so stoked
to see someone leave
in my life.
She hears me.
[chuckles]
That just means she hears me,
and I think this
is gonna allow Hannah
to really hone in
on what's good
for her future now.
And now she can go in with
an open heart and a open mind
and really choose
one of the men
that is good for her future.
- [sighs]
Dudes...
- [bleep]
- Oh, my God.
- Finally.
I'm so proud of Hannah
for just finally
just seeing it--
what we've seen
this entire time--
and just standing up
for herself,
and sending him home.
[laughs]
It was so badass, though,
when she just--
she took that rose stand
and moved it forward
and, like, wanted him
to get the hell out.
Absolutely.
- God, yes!
- [laughs]
Luke show is so [bleep] over
and that's...
we still have
a Rose Ceremony to go through,
but it's a good day.
- Oh, my God.
[laughter]
- Puke show is over.
- [exhales]
[low, unsettling music]
♪ ♪
- She still didn't understand.
- Coming up...
- If I could go back,
I wouldn't change a thing.
- "The Men Tell All"
continues...
Nothing?
When Luke takes the hot seat.
- I don't get to see her
straddle or mount
or swap saliva
with those other guys.
And I felt like I was on
a rescue mission for Hannah.
- And then...
- You are a narcissistic,
cantankerous, misogynist.
Your future wife is gonna be
a prisoner of you.
[audience exclaims]
- And later...
- I'm so over
being slut shamed.
- She's had plenty to say
about Luke all season.
- Did I sit around being like,
"Huh, who am I'm gonna have sex
with in the Fantasy Suites?"
No, I didn't.
- She's not finished yet.
- That wasn't
something planned,
and it wasn't your business
to ever ask me.
[cheers and applause]
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome back.
I am Chris Harrison.
We just watched
Luke's shocking return,
crashing the Rose Ceremony
in Greece
when he'd already
been kicked off the show.
So what happens after that?
Well, you're gonna have to
tune in next week to find out,
but for now,
let's hit the pause button,
and deal with
what we just witnessed.
Hannah is here
to spill the beans tonight,
answer all of our questions,
and all the guys,
they're here as well.
In fact, they are
backstage watching right now,
and, yeah, we have
a lot of questions for them.
It's gonna be an amazing night,
but we start tonight with
a man who's been at the center
of all this controversy.
We start tonight with Luke.
Luke, come on out.
[old Western music]
[sparse applause]
- [chuckles]
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
Come on in.
- Yes, sir.
♪ ♪
Oh.
[exhales]
- How are y--how are you doing?
Um...
'Cause even just this here is--
is very different
and very weird.
People aren't sure to applaud.
They're not sure how to feel...
- Right.
- So how are you feeling?
- So where do I begin?
Um...
- Well, it's something we'd
never seen on the show ever,
someone coming back like that
into the Rose Ceremony.
- Right.
- I think everybody's
still trying to process
what we just witnessed.
What were you hoping for?
- I said it--
clarity or closure.
I wanted one or the other,
and I really felt like Hannah
was making a huge mistake,
and she didn't even give me
a chance to speak my heart.
And if she would have given me
that opportunity,
I wouldn't have gone back.
I just wanted clarity
and, like I said, closure.
And I just felt like
the reason she sent me home
was because she thought
I was judging here,
which, I mean, you saw.
I went back because...
I was fighting for her.
- I think
what people will say is,
"Don't you think
that ship had sailed?"
And she did give you that time,
and when you said what you said
the night of what was gonna be
the Fantasy Suite
about, you know, "If you have
sex with somebody else
"or enjoy the Fantasy Suite,
I am recusing myself.
I'm stepping out of this,"
and things really melted down
between you.
You had your say,
it just went poorly,
and you wanted another say.
Right?
[audience laughter]
- Let me just clarify
so everyone can understand.
I had explained what I wanted
in marriage for me.
Talked about abstaining
from sex before marriage.
'Cause I'd be a fool to assume
and just continue this thinking
that we're on the same page,
and I asked her, I said,
"So have you or do you plan
on being sexually intimate
in the other relationships
in the Fantasy Suites,"
and that is when...
she--she turned from--from me,
and felt like--I could tell
she felt like I was judging,
which I was simply asking
a question,
um, for clarity for myself.
And she--she asked me--
and I quote--she said,
"Well, not saying
that I have had sex
"or that I haven't,
but let's say I have,
how would that change
how you feel?"
And I told her...
"To be honest,
I don't know what I would say,"
is what I told her,
and I said,
"I'd wanna approach you,
talk to you about it,
talk to you through it."
And then I said
right after that,
"But my initial reaction
would be,
"I'd want to remove myself
from the relationship,
and go home."
And that was only because
it's a deci--
decision for myself.
And I just want everyone
to be clear that...
my actions are because
I got completely blindsided,
and when I say
I was blindsided,
I mean...
kind of how she was handling
the whole conversation,
I just didn't expect
her reaction.
The fact that she's dating
these multiple guys,
and they're supposed
to be individual relationships,
you know,
I'm still looking at it
not as an unorthodox
dating situation.
I'm still looking at it
how I would date anyone,
and I don't get
to see anything that happens...
- Right.
- With Hannah
on the other dates.
I don't get to see her...
Straddle or mount
or swap saliva
with those other guys.
That's not easy,
and I just--
you know, I wouldn't want...
Someone that I'm li--
I'm literally getting fitted
for a suit to propose in,
and I'm finding out that
the night before
my one-on-one time with her,
she's having sex,
and that's not something
I wanted in a future wife.
- Oh, and by the way,
respect that
if that's your choice,
and in this particular case,
Hannah did make that choice
and that doesn't jive with you.
I'm--I'm a little bit surprised
you didn't just be like--
you didn't just walk away.
- I'm trying to think
of how to put this
so it's clear to you.
- Yeah.
- You know, I'm--I'm--
I made a mistake.
I made Hannah out to be
this perfect woman,
perfect wife for me,
with all the qualities that
I wanted in my future wife,
and...you know,
she said it herself,
she had a "love at first sight"
moment with me,
and she knew that I was one--
the one from the beginning.
It's something
she had shared with me.
Um, it wasn't
the fact that she had sex
that would just make me
completely want
to just leave her.
Again, I went in there, like...
going back to the Rose Ceremony
because I felt like
she was making a mistake,
and I really thought,
no matter what,
like, this is the one for me.
I've never felt
anything like this.
These feelings are real,
and I know they were real
for her,
and that's why you s--
that's why you see me
say things like,
you know, she's never told me
she loves me,
but I--like,
I believe that she does.
- Well,
I will corroborate the fact
that you were a frontrunner,
and she did say that
about love at first sight,
and you guys definitely had
a special relationship,
or it wouldn't have even gone
as long as it did, um...
- That's for sure.
- But it was also
extremely contentious,
and it really was--it all kind
of came back to the faith,
which is a debate
that we really have not had
at this depth on this show.
- Right.
- Your faith and her faith
and how you guys apply that
to your lives...
- Right.
- Is very different.
And it caused
a catastrophic event
in your relationship.
- I mean, I woul--
I would agree with that.
- What are you thinking
right now?
- I'm thinking of how to explain
everything that
you just mentioned...
Just so it can be clear.
It's, uh--
[chuckles]
It's a t--it's a tough one.
I'm sorry,
I'm getting choked up over here
just thinking about it.
The feelings were real.
I told her that I loved her.
Love is a commitment.
I was ready to fight
through anything with her.
That's why I went back for her.
I told her I was willing to
fight through anything with her,
and it didn't matter,
and that's why I-I went back.
It was frustrating,
you know, being misunderstood.
She totally thought
I was judging her,
and...
Yeah, I was--I was shocked.
I'd say shocked was definitely
the first emotion,
and...
Yeah, I was very confused.
You know,
Hannah brought up me with pride,
and, yes,
I did have a lot of pride,
and I was very arrogant
on the show.
- And she called you
a narcissist.
- Yes, exactly.
And that's something
that I struggled with heavy--
heavily on the show,
and that is something that,
you know,
I'm--I'm working on right now.
- So do you feel like
she was right in that respect?
- That's a tough question
because...
[audience exclaims, murmurs]
Again, I-I admit for being...
prideful and arrogant...
- Mm-hmm.
- But I think a narcissist
is pushing it a little far
because relationships are
a two-way street.
- Yeah.
Were you in love with her?
- Most definitely.
- Are you still
in love with Hannah?
- My feelings for Hannah...
Haven't changed.
I still love her.
I still want
what's best for her.
And I boldly say that.
But I also boldly say that
I know that she's not my person.
- Looking back...
Do you feel like
you made any mistakes?
- If I could go back,
I wouldn't change a thing.
[audience murmurs]
- Nothing?
[light laughter]
- [mouthing]
- All right,
wanna stop right there.
Luke, sit tight.
More with Luke P.
when we come back.
[applause]
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back
to "The Bachelorette:
The Men Tell All,"
an intense, emotional night
sitting here with Luke P.
All the guys are here.
Let me ask this again.
- Let me--let me just say this.
[laughter]
Where I'm coming from...
[indistinct shouting
and clapping]
[laughter, mocking]
You done over there?
All right.
Obviously, if I could go back,
I would change a whole lot,
but I'm just thankful that it--
it played out the way it did,
and I'm thankful
for the opportunity
to learn and grow as a man
from it all.
That's what I mean.
Now, you're talking about...
me and the guys
or just me and Hannah?
- You know what?
It could start with the guys.
'Cause maybe
that was part of it.
So just where you think
things went wrong for you,
and where you made mistakes.
- I think the turning point
with the guys really was...
was Rhode Island.
Being there...
in a situation where...
You know, I straight up...
bold-face lie to Luke S.,
and I did have the whole
sideline conflict with Luke S.
We'll leave it at that
and not get into details.
But...
you know,
it's tough when the house...
is in a position
where they think you're crazy,
you're a psychopath,
and you're a liar.
I watched the season.
I didn't like that Luke P. guy,
and I don't blame 'em for that,
but one of the hardest things
in this whole process
for me was,
you know,
on-camera/off-camera,
being neglected,
being disrespected,
having...
you know, been jabbed,
so to speak,
and come at by all the guys
constantly.
And then talk about
what was really hard--
is harder than that was...
the woman that I really thought
was the woman of my dreams
was struggling
of confiding in me,
and she was really questioning
my integrity
and my character
the whole process.
That was the hardest thing.
You know,
the guys was one thing,
but it was like
a two-headed dragon...
- Right.
- And it was--it was not easy.
You know,
from day one coming here,
you know, I felt like I was on
a-a rescue mission for Hannah.
That's how I--that's
how I like to look at it.
I really felt I was something
that was gonna be good for her
in a future husband.
- So when you say...
"rescue her"...
to me that means in your mind
she needed to be saved.
- Okay, let me--let me--
let me back up.
[laughter, dispersed booing]
I don't--I don't wanna be
misconstrued here, sorry.
When I say "rescue mission,"
um, I just meant from--
from them.
You know, I'm talking about,
uh, me thinking that,
you know, these guys,
regardless
if we're talking about
being there
for the right reasons
or if they're something that's
good for her in the future,
that's what I'm talking about
when I say "rescue mission."
- Um, the--the--
- I gotta go.
- Who is that?
- Man, I just gotta
call out [bleep] when I see it,
and I think that, ultimately...
- Devin.
- I'm gonna sit down
right here
'cause I just have
to say my piece.
- This is Devin, everybody.
[cheers and applause]
- Um...
[chuckles]
We've been backstage
watching this,
and, honestly, man, I've just--
my blood has been boiling.
Luke,
there are two type of men.
There's a--there are men
that want an independent,
strong woman,
and there are men that want
a woman that they can control.
I feel right now
that you are the man
that wants to control a woman
so that you can feel better
about yourself.
[cheers and applause]
And that--and I'm sorry--
I'm sorry, but that's not--
that's not a man.
That's not a man,
and what blows my mind
is you're saying that you--
you're--
you know,
you were on a "rescue mission,"
but it seems that the only
person that needed rescuing
was Hannah from you,
ultimately.
[cheers and applause]
I mean--
And I--and I understand
being young,
and it takes time to become,
like, a man and make mistakes,
but, dude, you had
a very long time of mistakes...
[applause]
So I can't--I'm sorry, Chris.
- No, no.
I'm gonna put a pin in this.
I appreciate you coming out.
- Yeah.
- Appreciate you coming out.
- I don't even get to share--
- No, no, well, you--
I'm gonna send him off.
I-I wanna finish up with you
and then--
'cause we are gonna
bring all the guys out.
Just--thanks, Devin.
I appreciate it.
[cheers and applause]
Um...
I just wanna finish up.
[applause]
But first I'll let you rebut
to what he was saying.
You know, was that--
is--is that something
you've thought about of
is that the type
of woman you want?
Someone you can kind of put
on the shelf in a glass case
and...pull down when you need?
- Just give a second, Chris.
- Mm-kay.
- The last thing that I want...
And the last thing
I'll ever do...
is control a woman.
And...
I do want an independent woman
in my life for my future wife.
I want a woman...
that will make decisions
for herself...
and that won't need me
when I'm there.
Although a man is supposed
to lead and guide a woman
in the relationship.
Now...
for you guys
watching me backstage,
you contestants,
I'm not here to argue.
[laughter]
I'm not here to argue
and defend myself,
so whoever's next to come out,
lay it on me.
- Well, all the guys
are about to come out.
[laughter]
[applause]
So are you ready for that?
- I'm ready.
- This has been
another fascinating chapter,
so thanks for being here.
When we come back,
the men are gonna join us
here on stage.
That's all coming up
when we come back
on "The Men Tell All."
[cheers and applause]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome back to
"The Men Tell All."
I am here with Luke,
and we were just talking
about his rather controversial
run here on the show,
but he's not the only one
on stage.
Nope.
All the men are back now,
and they are ready to tell all.
So let's welcome:
Ryan,
[cheers and applause]
Daron,
Brian,
Matt...
[cheers and applause]
Matteo,
Cam,
[dispersed booing]
Devin...
[cheers and applause]
Dustin,
Grant,
Jonathan,
John Paul Jones...
[uproarious cheers]
Luke S.,
Dylan,
Connor,
[uproarious cheers]
Garrett...
[cheering]
And Big Mike.
[uproarious cheers
and applause]
Fellas,
good to see you all again.
Thanks for being here,
got a lot to unpack
and get to tonight.
Obviously, we're gonna start
with the elephant in the room,
the man sitting next to me,
Luke.
Luke and I have been
out here talking.
I think you guys heard
a lot of it.
Luke, before I go up
to the guys,
people watching
and even myself,
sometimes I was like,
"Just--"
Like, "just fall on the sword.
Just fix it with the guys."
Like, "Just start fresh,
let's make it better."
You guys couldn't do that.
Like, you could never
get past that.
It just got worse and worse.
Why?
- You know,
the first few weeks
you could tell with my actions
that I had it in the bag.
You know, I really thought
that at some point
Hannah was gonna be like,
"All right, send the guys home,
"call the show.
It's Luke P."
You know, I did have
a target on my back of being,
you know, "frontrunner,"
getting the First Impression
Rose.
How is that not gonna
tick you off?
In my shoes, it was like
anything I said,
anything I did, any apology,
nothing was going to work.
And I did and tried my best
to do all of the above.
- You said that
for whatever reason
you have a target
on your back.
We didn't place that target
on you.
You put that target
on yourself.
I feel like we gave him
a clear slate,
just like we each gave
each other a clear slate.
He just went completely
out of his lane,
shall I say, um...
but then you continued to do
stupid crap.
- Yeah.
- I feel that Luke
hasn't learned
a thing whatsoever.
I think that you are
a narcissistic
cantankerous, misogynist.
I think that
your future wife
is gonna be a prisoner
of you...
[audience "Ooh"]
if you don't learn
how to change.
- [clears throat]
- We were coming from
a position of care
and wanted to say,
"Hey, there might be
some things you wanna
change up."
You never did,
and you still haven't shown
that you have changed tonight.
[applause]
- I mean, first off,
wanna give you
the only compliment
of the night
that you're gonna get
and just say that I do respect
you being here,
'cause you're about to step
into a firestorm.
But secondly, like,
every single week
there's a different event,
different situation,
that you had to apologize for.
And honestly,
it is one of those things
that actions speak
louder than words.
And we were waiting
for your actions to change,
but nothing ever changed
in what you did.
And so, you know, honestly,
I wish I had said this
earlier to you,
but just [bleep] you, man.
Like, you--I mean...
[cheers and applause]
- [mouthing]
- You--you're a liar,
manipulator,
you're controlling,
and you honestly are
a psychopath.
And I think everything
you're about to hear tonight
you deserve.
- I know you guys were watching
backstage
when I was talking
to Chris, and,
man, it hurt me to watch
that season
and to watch myself.
And I did make it about me,
and there's a lot of situations
that I acted
out of my own character,
and I was extremely prideful.
I boldfaced lied
to some of you guys.
I was extremely immature...
and I realize those things.
- So then why wouldn't you
change anything?
- And I hope that you guys
can support me
as I work on these things...
- Stop changing your story.
- And forgive me.
- I completely do not accept
your apology
that you just gave,
because 15 minutes ago
when we were backstage,
Chris asked you
a very respectful question,
"Would you change anything?"
You said, "No."
So why the hell would
any of us forgive you?
- You're apologizing--well,
a five-year-old who gets caught
with their hand
in the cookie jar
is gonna say "I'm sorry."
You always apologize
after the fact,
and you don't take
accountability for it.
Just the way you reacted
to her decision,
it bothered all of us to see
the way that you reacted
to that
and tried to tell her
what she could and couldn't do,
essentially.
It's just, like,
it's her decision, man.
Like, this is not up to you.
This is not about Luke P.
This is about Hannah.
[applause]
- What you owe a big apology to
is Peter, Jed, and Tyler.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- For your actions,
the way you handled
that last Rose Ceremony,
it was just so out of
your character and--
- Can I ask you what was
out of my character?
- Luke, when someone says "no,"
means "no."
Like, you're not here, like...
[cheers and applause]
I mean--I just...I mean,
do you guys agree?
- That--that--that's
an excellent point.
Yeah, I--
- I'm just saying.
Dude, it's, like, she took
the frickin' rose stand
and walked around you
and put it out here.
And you said,
"Well, I need some clarity."
What clarity--what else
you need?
- It's 2019, man.
You gotta wake up,
I want you to mature,
and you can't talk to a woman
like that.
Simple as that.
[cheers and applause]
- Luke, we didn't have
any immediate drama, you and I,
but I for one am thankful
for you,
because you're making me
look like a frickin' saint.
[laughter]
"No" means "no"
and "go" means "go."
Did you ever apologize to him,
by the way, for that?
Luke--Parker,
did you apologize to him
for body-slamming him?
- He did apologize to me.
- Luke--Luke S.,
did I apologize to you?
- You sure did,
but then the next night,
you went ahead and...
- [chuckles]
- You went
and told the group
"I'm gonna go tell Hannah
you're here
for the right reasons,"
and then did
the exact opposite.
- Right.
Looking back--
- Well, why did you do that?
- I...
- [snorts]
- [chuckles]
Oh, God.
- It's a very simple question.
Why did you do that?
- "I" is not an answer.
- I don't know.
- If I can just say,
for sure Luke messed up.
Luke made
a lot of bad decisions,
whether it was related to us,
related to Hannah,
whatever it was.
But at the same time, I mean,
even watching the episodes
that I wasn't a part of
after Rhode Island,
you could see the stress
and pain on Luke's face
about being socially isolated
from the group.
And I'm sure watching
these episodes
and being humiliated on TV
was not easy.
And to me, it feels like
he's already gotten
the punishment for his actions.
[applause]
- Luke, I'll ask--I'll
ask this question:
when you watched
the show back...
'cause you clearly stated
that you weren't judging her
and that that
was misconstrued...
- Yes.
- And I'm just curious,
because neither one of you
were there as a virgin.
- Yes.
- Like, you've had sex
and so has she,
so why was that
such a sticking point then?
Is there hypocrisy there?
- Not at all.
[laughter, murmuring]
Think about what you're asking.
Hannah--
[light laughter]
Hannah and I both had
conversations
about faith throughout
the whole process.
And there is
something called--I mean
there's many ways--you can
put it however you want,
some people say
secondary virgin, some say--
- Born-again.
- However you wanna put it.
I was asking questions
through conversation
to make sure that
I'm on the same page.
And after I had asked,
"Have you or have you not been
sexually intimate
in these relationships?"
And I was explaining to Hannah
that my initial reaction
would be to want
to remove myself
from the relationship,
and that's because
that's me making
a decision for myself.
- You and I connected on our,
you know, shared faith,
but after I left
and the way that you talked
and the way that you walked
was not Christian-like.
We all have our faiths.
We all go about it our own way,
but I think to project
that faith onto someone else
isn't the right way to do it.
[cheers and applause]
- I'll give you the final word
of anything you wanna say.
- It hurts me to hear
that some of you
don't accept my apology,
and I want you to know
that I'm sincerely sorry
about how it played out.
And I really hope
that you guys can forgive me.
[applause]
- Again,
thank you for being here.
It couldn't have been easy
to come sit in the hot seat
and take all of this tonight.
And a little bit later,
I'm sure there's gonna be more,
because you're gonna see Hannah
for the first time.
All of these guys are gonna see
Hannah.
So thank you for being here.
When we come back,
Hannah will be here.
What will she have to say
to men she sent home?
And later, you know 'em,
you love 'em,
we got bloopers.
All that and more
when we come back.
[cheers and applause]
Coming up...
- Fantasy Suites aren't used
for sex, Luke.
- Who will have
the final word
when Hannah faces Luke?
- Are you really telling me
that you never said:
"Don't judge me
about the Fantasy Suites,
because I won't be using that
for sex"?
[audience exclaims]
- Luke is really obsessed
with sex,
and I'm so over being
slut-shamed.
Like, I'm not gonna stand here
and feel that way.
[dramatic music]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome back to
"The Bachelorette:
The Men Tell All."
Look, it has been
an emotional night
and wanna get to everybody,
'cause everyone has a story
to tell.
And obviously,
Hannah is gonna be out here
a little later as well.
- I'd like--
I'd like to say something,
Chris, real quick.
- Just let it die.
Just let it die.
- Yeah.
- Let him speak, go ahead.
- I take full ownership
for everything
that I did on the show,
and I just want you guys
to know that
the whole process
was extremely tough for me,
and you guys still
don't know me.
You guys know me in
"The Bachelorette" bubble,
and I want you guys to continue
to see the man I am after this.
- Yeah, dude, I think we all
support you in, you know,
what's to come after the show,
but I think once we see
you've changed,
we'll accept your apology.
- I agree.
- Leave it at that.
- I look forward to it.
- Let's move on, shall we?
There are a lot of guys here,
and I wanna bring more of you
up to the hot seat,
'cause it really has been
one of the best seasons
of "The Bachelorette" ever.
First up, nobody stole
Hannah's attention
or Bachelor Nation's quite like
John Paul Jones.
While his time on the show
was quick,
it didn't take much for him
to become a fan-favorite.
So let's bring him up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
John Paul Jones.
[cheers and applause]
[all chanting]
John Paul Jones!
- I don't know
in the history of this show
if anyone's had
a better time...
- I mean--
- Every day on the show.
- I mean, when you get
to take off work
and, you know,
when everything's paid for.
You know, and Hannah's
a great girl, you know,
and it's kinda hard to,
you know, not have a good time.
[laughter]
- You had an amazing run
on the show, however brief.
It was a great ride.
I am not sure if you remember
any of it,
so let's take a look.
- [laughs]
[quirky music]
- Hi.
- Hello.
It's so nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hi.
So, my name is John Paul Jones.
- Okay.
- My friends call me
John Paul Jones,
so you can call me
John Paul Jones.
- John Paul Jones, that's it.
- Yeah.
- So I'll see you inside.
- Well, it's nice to meet you,
John Paul Jones.
Say "John Paul Jones"
three times fast.
John Paul Jones,
John Paul Jones.
Got it.
- John Paul Jones.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
[sultry music]
♪ ♪
- I think Hannah's looking
for a guy
that can be himself
no matter how awkward
or strange the circumstances
may be.
Today that guy could be me.
- Yeah!
Yeah!
John Paul Jones is a talent
in and of itself.
John Paul Jones!
He is definitely
making me smile.
- I wanted to let you cut
a piece of my hair.
- All right, stay still.
- Ah, I'm holding my breath.
Oh, God. All right.
Oh, man.
I definitely put myself
out there.
I mean, I didn't sign up
to, you know,
wuss out of anything.
- Now we would like you
to experience
this labor simulator.
- You gotta look at me.
- [yelling]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my G--ow!
- [yawns]
Ah!
[cackling]
[yells]
[laughs]
Oh, yeah.
Let's go, man.
Shaka brah.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, wow.
It's a little cringe-worthy,
but, you know, regardless,
I'm just grateful
for the experience.
Wouldn't have been easy
to have bro'd out
if you guys weren't so easy
to get along with.
So, you know,
all the attention,
you know, that I've gotten is,
you know,
attributed to you guys,
so thank you.
Appreciate it.
- What has life been like
for you
since the show started airing?
- You know, shortly after
my sort of experience,
things kind of normalized,
but when I go to the airport
and the gas station,
you know, I'll hear:
"John Paul Jones!"
You know?
You know, pretty frequently.
So I appreciate the good vibes.
Thank you all so much.
It's been interesting for sure.
- I love you, John Paul Jones!
- What's that?
- I love John Paul Jones.
- Oh, I appreciate it.
- I love that she has a--
- Can I come down there?
- Yeah!
- Whoa!
- Whoa.
- What's your name?
- I'm Siobhan.
- Hi, Siobhan.
I love the shirt, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks so much for the support.
- So nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
- I'm only slightly frightened
you have scissors.
- I do.
I do.
- [laughs]
What?
Oh, sure.
- I just wanted to say
I thought it was
the cutest thing ever
when you had Hannah cut
a piece of your hair off.
So, can I please...
- Yeah, go for it, sure.
- Cut a piece of your hair off?
- Why not?
Yeah.
- Be gentle.
- I'll be really gentle.
- Yeah, sure, go ahead.
- I'll do it from the back.
- If she says "I wanna wear
your skin as a suit,"
we're running.
- Okay!
- Okay, don't move.
- Okay.
- [groans]
- Yeah!
- All right, there we go.
Awesome, that was so great.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much
for the support.
I appreciate it.
- Oh, my God, of course.
Thank you.
- You're too kind.
I don't deserve it, thank you.
- Thank you.
Is that--is that, like,
normal life for you now,
people coming up,
cutting your hair?
- No--I mean, like,
people comment on that a lot,
and, you know, I don't
really have much to say
towards it.
It was sort of--I guess
my way of sort of
opening to Hannah.
- And just a little advice
as your friend...
- Yeah.
- Unless you wanna be bald,
you may wanna turn
some people down now
that wanna cut your hair.
If you keep saying yes...
- I know.
I get it, I get it.
It's funny.
- Speaking of fun,
we're gonna see you down
in Mexico.
- Um...
[cheers and applause]
I will take my Speedo
south of the border.
[laughter]
- It's gonna be a good time.
- Should be, yeah.
- You're up for some margaritas
and nuggets.
- Yeah, absolutely!
Absolutely.
- I've never met a man
that has such gusto and love
for chicken nuggets.
- How could you not, right?
- In honor of JPJ,
I'm bringing out nuggets
for everybody tonight.
[cheers and applause]
Chicken nuggets for everybody!
- All right.
[rock music]
- Thanks, Paulie.
There we go.
- Here we go.
Thanks for everything, man.
- Cheers, brother.
Cheers.
Here's to Paradise.
- Yeah.
- Those are good.
- Yeah, not bad.
Nice and warm.
- John Paul!
- [grunting]
[cheers and applause]
- Hey!
- Oh, God!
[laughter]
[cheering]
You guys, give it up
for John Paul Jones!
Can't wait to see you
down in Paradise.
- It'll be a good time,
for sure.
- I promise
there'll be nuggets.
When we come back,
Big Mike is here.
He's ready to open up about
that heartbreaking good-bye
in the Netherlands,
and later,
Hannah will be out here
to chat with us
about dating all of these men,
the good, the bad,
and the way, way worse.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome back to
"The Men Tell All."
Mike really lit up
Hannah's heart
with his million-watt smile
and charm.
And all the guys loved him,
Hannah fell in love with him,
so did Bachelor Nation.
So let's bring him up
to the hot seat, Big Mike.
[cheers and applause]
- Chris, man.
- Hi, brother.
Looking sharp, man.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Cute.
- I love you, Mike!
- I love you too.
- Look at you, man.
You're throwing smoke today.
- [laughs]
[laughter]
I'm really appreciative.
- You think about that
while we take a look back
at your time on the show.
[sentimental music]
- Hey.
- Hello there.
- How are you?
- I'm amazing.
You look wonderful.
- Aw, thank you.
- Hannah is
absolutely gorgeous.
She lived up to everything
and all my expectations
that I had of her and more.
- Hey!
Ah!
- I'm definitely 100%
feeling Hannah,
and I want this so bad.
I have three queens back home.
- Uh-huh.
- My younger sister,
my mother, and grandmother,
and I can see you being
my fourth and last queen.
The way Hannah makes me feel
is that I want more,
and I need to show Hannah
that I can be open.
My ex Leah got pregnant,
but we lost our child
in the second trimester.
And I wasn't there for her
at the time.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- And it's just one thing
that I can be a better man at.
- Mm-hmm.
- And quite honestly,
you give me hope.
You definitely do.
- Mike is honest and real
and can show
a vulnerable side emotionally.
It's so pretty.
Mike always comes to me
with a big smile
and always brings the energy.
I love it!
You look so cute!
We have a great time together
being silly,
and we also have a good time
being intimate.
- I can't stop smiling.
Our bond is very unique
and genuine.
I can see us creating a life
together.
I can see myself getting down
on one knee
if I'm ever so lucky.
I 100% can see her as my wife.
Are you okay?
[somber music]
- No, I'm not okay.
- What's on your mind?
Say it.
- [sniffles]
I think I've just been, like,
thinking a lot
since I've been here,
and, like,
we've talked about
your three ladies in your life.
They're so amazing, and, like,
you're looking for
your fourth lady,
and I know that
I'm not that fourth lady.
- [exhales]
- [sniffles, exhales slowly]
♪ ♪
- [sniffles]
Thank you, Mike.
Thank you.
- It's like her putting
a dagger in my heart
and tearing it out
and then stepping on it.
I know that I was opening
my heart up to Hannah,
and I know that
she crushed me.
'Sup, bro?
[chuckles]
- I know you put on
that brave face,
but that's tough.
That was tough to watch
and tough to go through.
- Yeah, it definitely was.
[exhales]
I just don't know, man.
During that nighttime portion
of the date,
I knew something was up
as soon as I got off
the elevator.
- Yeah, you could tell.
You could just feel it?
- Immediately.
And I was taken back.
It sucks when...
someone says that you deserve
to be fiercely loved,
as she told me,
and she knows in her heart
that she's not the one
to give it to me.
- You were really starting
to see this woman
be a big part of your life,
as you said,
be that fourth pillar...
- Yeah.
- Of all those strong, amazing
women in your life.
And you thought, "Maybe this
could be the other one."
- Definitely so.
I mean, I've brought
one woman home in ten years.
I take this stuff
incredibly serious.
I felt that I could see myself
getting down on one knee
if it continued to progress
the way it was.
- I know that's not something
you throw around lightly.
- It would have been amazing
for her to see and meet
my mother and my sister
and my grandma.
I grew up with all ladies,
and I know I've learned
so much.
And I just wanted to give
all the things I've learned
to a woman so deserving
as Hannah.
- You're gonna see her today.
You thought about that,
what it's gonna feel like?
- Um...she said,
"Mike, you deserve to be
"fiercely loved.
You're this great,
you're that great, but..."
You know?
And I just want to know
what that "but" was
for me, personally, so that
I continue to grow as a man.
- So you'd like a little
closure here tonight.
- I do want closure, as a man.
And I wanna make sure that
she is okay
in what she's going through
and to let her know that
I still think
she's fine as hell
and she's independent.
- Well, I appreciate you
coming down.
- Thank you.
- It's good talking to you.
- You guys, give it up
for Big Mike.
Before we move on,
I have some exciting news
for you, Bachelor Nation.
We're about to launch
an exciting new way
to experience "The Bachelor."
It's called
"Bachelor Live On Stage"
hosted by Ben Higgins,
and it's coming to a city
near you.
If you've ever wondered
what it's like
to be on "The Bachelor,"
then this is your chance.
Tickets go on sale July 26th.
Go to BachelorLiveOnStage.com
for more information.
All right, the time has come.
When we come back,
Hannah will join me
right here on stage.
And you know what happens
when you uncage the Beast.
Actually, I don't.
We'll find out.
We'll be right back.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
Up next...
- I'm so over being
slut-shamed.
- It's Hannah's turn
to tell all.
- I'm not gonna stand here
and feel that way,
and you're not gonna make me
feel that way.
- And there's no holding back.
- Luke is really obsessed
with sex,
and I'm not gonna say that
me having sex in a windmill
was just, like,
the scarlet letter on my chest.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[exciting music]
- Welcome back to
"The Bachelorette:
The Men Tell All."
Well, it is happening.
It's time.
Ladies and gentlemen, Hannah!
[cheers and applause]
- Hi.
Hey, guys!
[laughs]
- Take a seat.
- Whoo!
- It's always good
to see you again.
- It's always great to be here
with you.
- Is it, in front of all
your ex-boyfriends?
- Oh!
Oh, hello there!
[laughs]
You all look great.
You know,
seeing one ex-boyfriend,
it's kinda like, "Oh, hey."
- Yeah, 20?
- Seeing--yeah, all of 'em,
it's like, surreal, surreal.
- A little overwhelming.
- Yeah.
- Most people
don't have to face this.
- But I am really glad
to see you guys.
I'm just so blessed to have
had you on this ride with me
and that you did stick it out
with me
through some of my decisions
that you might not have
agreed or understood.
And so I just wanna say
thank you.
- You know what, as you have
watched this show back,
what moments or what things
stood out to you
that maybe you didn't catch
living it in real time?
And you go,
"How did I miss that?"
- Well, I think it has to,
like--I have to back it up
from the very beginning
with my relationship with Luke.
I will never try to say
that the feelings
that I had for him
weren't real,
because they were.
It was the closest thing
that I had
to feeling love at first sight.
But I think a lot of that
came from...
being really insecure
about being the Bachelorette
in the first place.
- Interesting.
- I remember when I got
the call from you.
I was so excited,
but also I had this doubt
of "Oh, my gosh, like,
are the guys gonna be
disappointed?"
And "Am I gonna be able
to live up to this standard
that I thought I had
to live up to?"
And the first night there,
there is this huge fear
of what your intentions are.
And that night,
Luke made me believe
that he was there for me
and gave me hope
from the beginning.
And I held on to it
a lot longer
than I should have,
but it gave me safety.
"Okay, at least one guy's here
for me."
- That's interesting.
- And you can't do that
in a relationship.
You have to actually look.
- That's incredible
perspective.
- Ultimately,
I'm really glad that
that relationship's
behind me
and that I can move forward
from that
and I've learned a lot
from the experiences
that I went through.
I deserved so much more than
what I kind of put up with.
[cheers and applause]
- Luke, this is the first time
you've had a chance
to see Hannah.
What would you like to say?
- You know, I really don't have
much to say,
just the fact that I'm sorry
that I made the whole process
for you so difficult.
And I will say too--I will say
thank you.
You know, you actually did
teach me a lot as well,
about myself.
Taught me how to self-reflect,
and you showed me how important
it is to open up.
So I will say thank you
for that.
So that's all I have.
[applause]
- [laughs]
I appreciate those words.
Um...you know, you said
that you learned from this,
and I do hope that you did.
Um...but...
I think that there's a lot
of fruit that needs to be grown
from you.
[sighs]
I don't know.
I don't even know
what I can say.
- You know what, much has been
made of his faith,
your faith, religion,
and how all of that
played into this,
and there was that as well.
'Cause your faith is important
to you.
- Mm-hmm.
Absolutely.
From the first night,
it was one of our first
conversations,
and I wanted a man of God
that had those same values,
but then that was almost
weaponized against me.
I was, at the end,
threatened by the shared faith
that we had.
And unfortunately,
the people that believe
the same thing I do
do that a lot sometimes,
of using the same words
and the same things we believe
to call out specific things
and poke...
- Right.
- And so the basis
of what I believe is love
and loving others
and understanding
and not shaming.
And his love was contingent on
if I did the things
that he wanted me to do
as he saw as a wife should do,
not an unconditional love.
- You talk about being shamed.
That brings up the night
of your Fantasy Suite.
- Mm-hmm.
- On that final date with Luke.
Did you feel shamed
in that moment?
- Well, yeah.
Luke is really obsessed
with sex
and the Fantasy Suites
being about sex
and so I'll just tell everybody
my sex life.
But honestly,
did I sit around being, like,
"Huh, who am I gonna
have sex with
in the Fantasy Suites?"
No, I didn't.
That wasn't something planned,
that wasn't something that
really was everybody's business
to know.
- Right.
- And it wasn't your business
to ever ask me.
[uproarious cheers
and applause]
- Are you really telling
that you never said:
"Don't judge me
about the Fantasy Suites,
because I won't be using that
for sex"?
- I did not say that.
Fantasy Suites aren't used
for sex, Luke.
You didn't have one
so maybe you don't know,
but the Fantasy Suites
aren't used for sex.
- That's my girl!
There you go!
- And now looking back,
it wasn't just that moment.
Like, I had been blind
to everything
that had been happening.
I did listen to you guys,
but I knew if I had listened to
one of you guys say
what he did,
I would always have, like,
a "what if," or a--ugh,
that feeling
when, like, you--when
a relationship ends,
but there's still something
there.
And I didn't want that
for myself.
- You didn't make up
your own mind.
- I didn't make up my own mind.
I'd just be listening
to what was happening.
I needed to feel it and see it
for myself.
And that night I felt it
and saw it for myself,
and that was when it
just snapped for me.
Now I'm like, "I will not
put up with this,
"because that's not love,
"that's not what the person
I wanna spend
the rest of my life with
is ever gonna make me feel."
And I'm so over being
slut-shamed
and being felt like
that makes me
not a woman of faith.
Because--oh, my gosh, like,
I live my life
and make mistakes and sin
every single day and so do you
and so do you
and so do you and so do you
and so do you,
but that's what grace is for.
And I'm also not gonna say that
me having sex in a windmill
was just, like,
the scarlet letter
on my chest to have.
Like, I'm not gonna stand here
and feel that way,
and you're not gonna make me
feel that way
and that I maybe did that
in my relationship,
I'm not, and...
[cheers and applause]
And those Fantasy Suites,
that's not what
they were about.
It was about having
a relationship
where I grew really close
to the men
and knowing their heart.
It's not just about
the physical,
and that's where you're getting
it really, really wrong
and misconstruing me
as an individual
and anybody who's ever gone
into a Fantasy Suite before.
- Does that make sense?
- Yes.
- I'm sure us--standing
with the rest of us,
we completely support you.
And we trusted you
and listened to you
and followed your heart
and we know that you did
the right thing in your time,
so we completely have your back
in that.
- Thank you for that.
[applause]
- It is a good group of guys
and a lot more guys
I wanna get to
beyond just Luke.
- Yeah.
- So we'll do that....
- Okay.
- Right after we take
a quick break.
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Welcome back to the Tell All,
and as we were coming back,
Luke just got up and left.
So there you go.
He's catching a flight,
but I think we're good,
'cause I think that is
a perfect symbol
of let's move on.
You were talking with Big Mike
right before we went
to the break there,
and I wanna go back.
What would you like to say
to Mike?
- I just wanna say thank you.
That good-bye was really hard
for me,
because we had that connection
that saying good-bye to you
felt like
I was really miss--like,
losing something.
To know that you had
supported me the whole time
and constantly been
my cheerleader
and know that I am just so glad
that you were on this journey
with me
and that I respect you
and will be your fan forever.
So I'm sorry and you deserve...
- Don't apologize.
Don't apologize.
- The best, and I'm rooting
for you for the best.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- Who else wanted to say
something to Hannah?
- Hey, Hannah.
- Hey, Garrett.
- Good to see you again.
- It's good to see you too.
- You look great.
Um...
I'll come out with it.
I was pretty upset with you
for a while.
You taught me so much.
You helped me open up a lot.
But with that...
I just was so hurt that
you did choose him over me.
But I wanna say I'm sorry,
because watching it back,
it's now more clear
that you were misled,
like, big time.
And I'm sorry that
you had to go through that,
and I'm wondering
if any of us
could have actually done
anything to really help you
see that,
even more than what we did.
- So I--there's so many
"what ifs" that I could done.
There's so many times I'm like,
"Oh, my gosh,
"if they would have
just told me this,
maybe I would have known."
- We were scared.
- Yeah, I know,
because I would tell you
to stay in your frickin' lane.
- We were scared.
- I am kind of scary, I know.
But I...I don't regret
the way that it happened,
because I feel like...
the relationship
that I had with Luke...
Unfortunately,
it's a relationship
that a lot of women
can relate to.
- Yeah.
- A lot of women have been
in toxic relationships
and maybe just maybe
me going through that
and being able
to remember my worth
and figure that out for myself
can help somebody
that's in that now
and see the signs of that.
And ultimately,
that makes me realize
that I don't have regrets,
because that was worth
all of it.
[cheers and applause]
- But...Luke aside,
I think what America
really wants to know,
how did you let JPJ go?
[laughter]
'Cause that makes no sense
to anybody.
- No, I get it.
Don't worry about it.
It's cool.
I don't hold anything
against you.
Like, I would have
let myself go if I were you.
Don't--don't worry about it.
- Do not talk about yourself
like that, JPJ.
- Don't tell me what to do,
Hannah.
[laughter]
- You guys just had
your first fight.
Hey, we had a lot of drama.
- Yeah.
- But we also had a lot of fun.
- Fun.
- Yeah, no shortage of fun,
and so I think
it's finally time.
Let's lighten things up.
I never get tired of 'em.
- Oh, gosh.
- Bloopers.
[cheers and applause]
All right, first limo.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Hey, good luck.
Hannah...
- I'm gonna be okay.
- Let the journey begin.
Here it comes.
- Oh, [bleep] me.
Oh, shoot.
My dress is stuck!
Oh!
- Now we would like you
to experience
this labor simulator.
- [moaning]
- Ooh.
Breathe.
- Oh, Chris Harrison.
- Chris Harri--why are you
calling out Chris Harrison?
- Oh, John Paul Jones!
Wow, mother of [bleep]!
Okay.
Okay, I'm out!
I'm out!
[romantic music]
♪ ♪
- [laughing] I'm sorry,
I'm just laughing because...
- What?
- He's standing on top
of the bench.
- Pretend that he's not there.
- Yes, queen.
"Yas," queen.
Yas, queen.
Ya....okay, here's a good one.
Yaaas, queen.
Yaas, queen.
- Man.
- John Paul Jones,
will you accept this rose?
- Yaas, queen.
- ♪ Hannah,
you are not from Montana ♪
♪ I wanna peel you
like a banana ♪
- Work, work, work.
[upbeat hip-hop music]
♪ ♪
Roll.
Okay, I'm done.
- ♪ I said we got a Riga ♪
- ♪ I said we a got a Riga ♪
- ♪ We need a Riga ♪
- Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh!
- Give it to me!
- [yells]
- Mike.
- What are y'all doing?
- Morning.
[clangs]
- Oh...
- It's paid for.
- Oh, [bleep].
- That's all right,
the limo's paid for.
- I can't turn.
I can't make the turn!
[groans]
Okay.
- There.
- [gasps]
[laughter]
[applause]
- There was a lot of drama,
but we leave with a smile
on our face.
- That's right.
- Thanks for being here.
I appreciate it.
- Thanks for having me.
- It's good to have you.
What?
- Wait, I just have, like,
one thing that I wanna say.
- Well, it's your show,
why not?
- I just want to say...
Bachelor Nation, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for this whole thing
with Luke
and him just being
on our television screens
for so long,
way longer than
really any of us ever desired.
Um, it's my fault,
a lot his,
but I did it.
I was there.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired of talking about him.
Chris, are you tired
of talking about him?
- Amen.
- Are y'all tired of
talking about him?
all: Yes!
- The Luke P. show is canceled.
We will not renew
the season.
Again, my apologies
and God bless the United States
of America.
Roll tide.
- You guys,
give it up for Hannah!
[cheers and applause]
We have to take a quick break,
but when we come back,
we have a preview
of the unforgettable conclusion
to Hannah's journey
and then an exclusive
first look
at the new season
of "Bachelor in Paradise."
All that when
"The Men Tell All" returns.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Welcome back.
Next week Hannah's epic journey
for love will come
to a dramatic conclusion.
It's down to Peter, Jed,
and Tyler,
and an impossible decision.
Who will Hannah pick?
Will they propose?
Will Hannah have
her happily ever after
with the man of her dreams?
It's all a part of a historic
two-night live finale
that you absolutely
cannot miss.
Here's a dramatic sneak peek.
[dramatic music]
- Oh, my God.
- You don't know what to do,
right?
- I'm freaking out.
It's really, really hard.
And now I have a lot of doubt
and fear.
[sobbing]
- Who is Hannah's
one true love?
- I can tell you have concerns,
will you just--will you just
say 'em?
- I don't want you to settle
for anything.
And that's as honest
as I can be.
- How will Hannah decide
between the men she loves?
- [bleep] me.
This is why you don't date
two people at the same time.
- I want somebody that would
love you like I know
you should be loved.
- Her life changing decision
is made next week.
- I've been waiting
my whole life
to have my happy ending,
but I just feel like
this experience
has been taken away from me.
I can't do this.
- Don't miss
the dramatic season finale.
- Can you stop the car?
[grunts]
I really can't do this.
- And then in two weeks...
all: Paradise!
[cheering]
- [rolls tongue, cheers]
- It's the exciting new season
of "Bachelor in Paradise."
- The party has arrived!
- Yeah, baby!
- Ay, papi.
You're making me hot.
[laughter]
- All of your favorite
Bachelors and Bachelorettes
are back on one beach.
- I can say with confidence
that I've never met anybody
like John Paul Jones.
- Sorry, Mom.
I'm with a really
beautiful woman right now.
- This is so crazy!
- Dean's mustache absolutely
swept Caelynn off her feet.
- There's a lot of maintenance
that goes into
keeping this thing
as beautiful as it is.
- And nothing
will ever be the same.
- So Blake slept
with Kristina.
Blake slept with Caelynn.
Is he sleeping with Tayshia?
Is he sleeping with Hannah?
Did he bang Chris Harrison?
[laughter]
- Blake's in a love decagon.
Hannah's in a triangle.
I just want to find
one person to love.
I don't need a posse.
- In Paradise,
love is for everyone.
- Oh, my God,
you're my husband.
[both laughing]
Oh, my God.
- [squealing] Goose babies.
Yes.
- I don't care who sees this.
I know that I love this girl.
I'm just so happy
that I found her,
and I can definitely picture
being with her
for the rest of my life.
- I know for a fact,
deep down,
I'm the one
who's so ready for love,
so ready for marriage.
- The Fantasy Suite awaits.
- This feeling right here is
why I came to Paradise.
- We've progressed so much,
and I would love to spend
this extra time
with you
in the Fantasy Suite.
- [laughing]
Oh, this is crazy.
- But so is the drama.
- Last night, Demi and I had
a really fun time
in the hot tub.
That's not something
I should have to hide.
- You can't help who you love,
and it hurts me to see you
struggling.
- I, like, just don't want to
lose you.
- [screaming]
- He's putting his spoon
in all the pudding.
- What the [bleep]
is happening?
- Bitch!
- [bleep] you, I'm done.
- They're, like,
actually fighting.
- You guys, no!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
- [bleep]
Watch your back, [bleep].
- Don't miss
all the heartbreaking drama.
- Don't insult
my intelligence, Derek.
You're full of [bleep].
You take advantage of women.
Get out of my sight!
- And more crying
than ever before.
- [sobbing]
- All I want is happiness
for myself and other people.
- This is hard.
[both weeping]
- [crying] Oh, man.
This is so hard, dude.
I don't know if I can do this.
I don't know if I can [bleep]
do this, man.
- I just gotta get out of here,
man.
I gotta get out of Paradise.
- But in the end,
it's all about love.
- I smell an engagement,
and it feels amazing.
- Oh, my God!
Yes!
- Every Monday
and every Tuesday
all summer long.
[cheers and applause]
"Paradise" is right around
the corner!
It premieres August 5th.
It is, dare I say,
the most dramatic season
of "Paradise" yet.
That's right, I said it.
You're welcome.
And don't miss
the exciting conclusion
to Hannah's story
during our dramatic two-night
live finale coming up
on July 29th and 30th
right here on ABC.
I know there are a lot
of rumors out there right now.
I promise all of your questions
will be answered.
Gentlemen,
thanks for being here.
To our studio audience,
thank you all very much.
And to you, Bachelor Nation,
as always,
thanks for being a part of it.
For everyone who's been
a part of this one,
I'm Chris Harrison.
Good night, everybody.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I do have one final thing
to say and um...
I need to kind of stretch
and stand to say...
- Oh, God, oh, God.
- Don't do it.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, okay,
y'all already moaning?
So, how 'bout this?
Uh...
- Oh, boy.
- Oh, no.
- ♪ Crashing one group date
does not make me a stalker ♪
♪ I could have looked worse
like my name is Luke Parker ♪
♪ John Paul Jones
on the screen ♪
♪ You know that we love it
as much as his hair ♪
♪ And we like
the chicken nuggets ♪
♪ Got love for all y'all ♪
♪ And most of y'all my bros ♪
♪ Even forgive those who say
I wanted a pity rose ♪
♪ But this is for the girl
that we call Hannah ♪
♪ Y'all can see me
in Paradise ♪
♪ Cam in a cabana ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Well done, dude.
Well done.
- Give it up for Cam!
[cheers and applause]
- That's talent.
- ABC, baby, ABC.